carrentals.co.uk 2018-08-12

# Cheapest Car Hire Prices Found With One Search

This website is managed by EasyTerra B.V.

The company is domiciled at:

Westersingel 24  
8913 CL Leeuwarden  
The Netherlands

This policy statement describes, among other things, which information is collected on this website, why we do so and how we use the information.

### 1\. Why does EasyTerra B.V. collect information?

We sometimes ask you to provide personal information on this website, such as name, email, address, telephone number, age, whether you have a driver's licence and your interests. We may supplement these details with information we have received about you via third parties. We use this information for the following purposes:

  * We may approach you for newsletters, offers and useful tips/information. However, we will always explicitly ask for your consent.
  * To better match our future services to your needs.

### 2\. How safe is your data with EasyTerra B.V.?

We consider it absolutely essential to treat the information of our users as safely as possible. EasyTerra B.V. has taken the following measures for this purpose:

  * Payments take place in a secured environment: 
    * We use secure connections, in technical terms a 256-bit encrypted Secure Socket Layer (SSL) certificate which can be recognised by the web address starting with https:// instead of the common http://. This implies that messages are encrypted and that any messaging between you and our website cannot be intercepted by third parties.
  * We only use credit card information to process payments; the details are not stored on our server. This minimises the risk of improper use of your credit card details.
  * We use the most up-to-date software on our servers, hereby minimising break-in attempts.

### 3\. To whom may we disclose your personal information?

We may ask third parties to process and analyse personal information we have requested from you.

We are sometimes required to provide information to third parties when we purchase a product or service from them.

It may also be necessary to provide your personal information to a third party in order for that party to provide the product or service you ordered (in this case we operate as intermediary).

We will provide your personal information to the authorities if compelled to do so.

### 4\. Which personal information and data do we collect?

Some information is collected using cookies.

Cookie: a text file that is stored by servers on your computer's hard drive.

A cookie contains:

  * Information about you as a visitor of that particular site
  * Information to store your passwords, user names and preferences for that particular site

You may adjust your browser to reject cookies but this will make the site less user-friendly.

We also collect information about your computer/computer usage such as:

  * IP address: this is only stored if you place messages (if applicable to the site) on the website. We do so to exclude possible unwanted authors of messages from the site (to be able to stop abuse).
  * Type of internet browser
  * Type of operating system
  * Requested URL
  * Time of website visit
  * http-referer-url (possibly including the search terms you used in a search engine)
  * Your search and how you performed it (via which search engine, using which search terms, etc.)
  * User-agent-string
  * Screen size

All this information is stored and updated in log files on our servers. This information may subsequently be linked with other data we have collected from you.

The objective of collecting and possibly linking this information is to better match our services and products with your needs and interests.

### 5.Advertisement displays and clicks

Advertisement displays and clicks are registered by us and advertising networks in which our company participates. This information is collected for purposes including:

  * Financial accountability between us and the advertising network
  * Statistical information with which we try to optimally promote our products but also to tailor them as closely as possible to your needs

EasyTerra B.V. uses the following advertising networks: 

  * [Google Adwords Content Network](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) (this party has its own privacy policy)

By displaying advertisements and web beacons these advertising networks can place cookies (see under 4) on your computer.

Web beacons are invisible images embedded in the website which serve to track who has read that page.

### 6.Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service offered by Google.

This program uses cookies to help us analyse how visitors use our site. Google saves the information collected on servers in the United States.

Google may disclose this information to third parties if legally required to do so or if Google calls in third parties to process the information.

### 7.If you do not wish to receive targeted information

We may use the information you provided to approach you via email, telephone and email.

If you do not wish to receive information from us, you can inform us and request us not to send you any further information.

We will make it as easy as possible to unsubscribe from newsletters etc.

### 8.Interactive parts of our websites

If you participate in interactive parts of our website (forums, membership site, learning environment, feedback environment, etc., you need to fill out certain information. In addition you may publish information on these interactive parts. As you personally disclose this information, you assume responsibility for possible consequences resulting from this publication. We bear no responsibility for information that is published by you (or on your behalf).

If you do wish to participate in the interactive parts of our website but want to remain as anonymous as possible, you are free to apply the following:

  * Use a pseudonym
  * Use an email address that cannot easily be traced back to you

### 9.Disclaimer

We accept no liability for the information placed by visitors on the interactive parts of our websites. The information published by visitors are personal opinions of the authors and do not bear any relationship with the opinions/views/positions etc. of EasyTerra B.V.

Although we compile the information on this website with the utmost care, we cannot guarantee that the information provided is correct and/or complete. EasyTerra B.V. accepts no liability for damages incurred or to be incurred in the future as a result of incorrect or incomplete information on the website.

On our websites we refer to other websites/companies/persons, etc. by means of hyperlinks, banners, buttons, acknowledgements, etc. This reference does not imply a connection between EasyTerra B.V. and the other website and/or its owners/those responsible. We therefore accept no liability for adherence to privacy legislation by the third parties concerned.

### 10.Misuse

If we are of the opinion that facilities on our website are misused, we may take measures including: 

  * Denying access to certain IP numbers for an unlimited amount of time
  * Denying access to certain email addresses for an unlimited amount of time
  * Denying certain persons access for an unlimited amount of time
  * Transferring the relevant information to a third party, should harm have been caused to the third party concerned
  * Trying to trace your information back to you in order to contact you or your parent, guardian, supervisor, person responsible, etc.
  * Notifying the police which may lead to us suing you

We will provide your information to the authorities if compelled to do so.

### 11.What are your rights?

You may ask EasyTerra B.V. to disclose which of your data is being processed. We will respond as quickly and satisfactorily as possible.

You may ask us to adapt or, if required, remove the information.

### 12.Possible changes to this privacy statement

EasyTerra B.V., at its discretion, reserves the right to change this privacy statement.

### 13.Questions and requests: Where do you go?

In the event of questions and/or requests regarding this privacy statement / your privacy, you may contact us at:

EasyTerra B.V.  
Westersingel 24  
8913 CL Leeuwarden  
The Netherlands

We only consider requests and/or questions submitted in writing.

### 14.In conclusion

This privacy statement shall be governed by the law of The Netherlands.
